[{"answer": "I'm great, Piers.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "David, how are you?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Well, we were very, very happy with the debate.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "Are things a little chipper, more chipper down there than they were after the first debate?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "Not - it doesn't really worry me, Piers, because I saw a whole bunch of data off of that debate including other polls and focused groups and dial groups.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "And that's got to worry you, hasn't it?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Well, let me say a few things about that first, Piers.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "These are huge sticks to beat you guys with, aren't they?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "Well, look, I think what the president said last night was very, very clear.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "Do you accept as the administration that there were failings here?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "Piers, there are -- I don't know, I think 270 installations around the country and all of those go into the security professionals at the State Department who make judgments based on their expertise as to what is done.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Does he never see any request of that nature?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "Well, I think the binders for women formulation was an awkward formulation.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Do you guys think that perhaps you should be focusing on more serious stuff than this?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "Yes, we -- this is a reality we live in, not just in the New York City area, all over the country.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "It reminds everybody of the ever present danger of a rogue terrorist element in whatever guise they come, isn't it?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "Well, clearly the phrase \"act of terror\" was in the speech that was given in the Rose Garden.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "Why shouldn't Candy Crowley have jumped in when she did?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "Not to my mind.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "But he was clumsy, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "Perhaps.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "He should have phrased it a different way?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Yes, I don't this changes the momentum or the dynamics of the race at all.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Is that the way you see it?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "I don't think there is clear momentum surging behind Mitt Romney.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "And are you getting very worried about what you are seeing in the polls, which is clear momentum now surging behind Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "Well, it's interesting, because the first question, I was pleased to see, came from a college student.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "What did you make of the debate last night?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "And meanwhile, you have a huge missed opportunity.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "So both candidates are way off the mark, you think?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "So, I think this is one of those ones where I actually view Mitt Romney as having the potential -- he's coming in I think a bit as the under dog, but has a really strong hand.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "Who is going to win that, and who has the stronger position on foreign policy?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "I think you have to do a lot more.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Not a bad resume, isn't it, on the old -- on the old ticket in the first term?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "I'd say two things.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Matt, very, very quickly, the youth view of this?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "The average young person probably is for Barack Obama on foreign policy, because he ended the war and he has a clear record.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "Who do you trust more, Romney or Obama on foreign policy?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "It appears not at this point.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "Nobody really wants to do anything about government control, do they?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "Yes, I am.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "Disappointed?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "Again, I wasn't really impressed by the answers, were you?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "If Mitt Romney wins, he said I'll have a job by the time I graduate in 2014.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "Are you more likely to get one if Barack Obama or Mitt Romney wins, from what you heard last night?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Did you believe him?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "I thought neither question during the debate was on point.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "What was your overview, by the time you look back on it, about how they answered?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "He told me that the cause for delay between the Rose Garden announcement and the 14 day official terrorist announcement was because he wanted to be deliberate, that any action he took anywhere in the world, especially in the Middle East, could cause irreparable harm, and he wanted to act on true information, not misinformation.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "What did he say to you?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "Yes, I spoke to Governor Romney and I spoke to President Obama.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "Nina, did they talk to you, the candidates, afterward?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "I was anxious to hear President Obama's reaction.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "Did either of them give you any glimmer of hope about gun control or not?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "Not so much Romney, he was not -- but President Obama came by, thanked me for the question, and said it was a good question.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "Carol, did you get anything from either of them afterwards?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "I talked a little bit with Barack Obama's campaign people.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Jeremy, either of them personally say, look, you can come and work for me?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "I guess so.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "So is it quality time then?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "ORGAN: President Obama.", "docId": "121017pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "I haven't completely made my mind up, but I lean towards President Obama?", "qSentId": 574}]